Alexey Melentev

Phone number: 380967287040

E-mail: meleldorado@gmail.com

Skype: duriccs



Junior Front-End Developer

Resume in web format: https://github.com/AllXeight/Alexey Melentev.git

Skills summary:

- HTML5 & CSS3, JS, Bootstrap 4
- GitHub (AllXeight)
- currently studying: GULP, SASS, ES, TS

About myself:

I graduated from the Technical University and I have a degree in Information Systems and Technologies.

I had been working as a system administrator and an information security specialist in enterprises, but there were other specialties as a manager!

Now I am ready for a new challenge, that's why I applied for this position in your company.

I enjoy solving problems, troubleshooting issues, and coming up with solutions in a timely manner.

Experience:

- Leading Data Protection Specialist at Motor-Bank, May 2015 - May 2017

Development of algorithms for the protection of confidential information and their implementation in organizational documents. Directly work with confidential information and actions related to its maintenance!

- Security Specialist, Regional Leader at Skvortsovo, Oct 2012 - Dec 2014

Organization and control over the work of the enterprise, conducting interviews, checking personnel, maintaining stable operation of security systems, working with receivables!

- Security Systems Specialist, Deputy Head of Security Service (for technical matters) at RIST, Aug 2009 – Jan 2011

Organization and control over the work of the security service, conducting interviews, checking personnel, maintaining stable operation of security systems, creating and implementing a database of access control systems, and developing algorithms to provide access to the enterprise for about 1,200 employees in three work shifts!

Education:

Zaporizhia National University Application programmer, specialist, 2009

Zaporizhia National University Computer Science, Master, 2012

ITVDN - IT school, 2018-2019:

JavaScript Essential Certificate
JavaScript Advanced Certificate
HTML5 & CSS3 Advanced Certificate

Language skills:

English - Elementary